記一下你們的假期作業
All of you, write down the homework you have to do.
課後習題第32至38題
Problem number 32 to 38 on the sheet.
然後呢?-然後？
And? - And?
-就這些-就這？
And that's it. - That's it?
拜亞哥，我們有五天的假期
Bhaiya we have five days off.
再加點作業吧，我們能做完的
Give us some more. We will do it.
是的，我知道，所以不再加了
Yes, I know. That's why I am not giving you more.
這五天是學校的實踐日
These five days are for the school's practical.
你們都好好放鬆一下，好嗎？
All of you will focus on that and relax. Okay?
放鬆？
Relax?
是的，改組考試將在假期結束後的第15天進行
Yes. And your reshuffling exams will be held in 15 days of returning.
13天，拜亞哥-對，13天
13 days, sir. 13 days. - Listen. 13 days.
到時候你們再像個瘋子一樣學習
Then you have to study like a lunatic then.
是時候給你們的電池充充電了
Charge your battery a little.
好好放鬆一下，緩解壓力
You won't burn out if you relax a little along with your studies.
但是你們所有人都要把註意力放在學校上
But all of you will focus on school.
烏代，你在想什麼?-冇什麼
Uday, what's on your mind? - Sir.
這並不意味著你們就可以懶散了
That doesn't mean all of you laze completely. Just sleeping.
冷靜一點
Chill a little.
你們中有多少人明天一早要去上學？
How many of you will be going to school for the first tomorrow?
舉起手來
Put your hands up.
太棒了! 你們都是未來的國家棟梁
Bravo! This is the cream of our country.
非常好！
Very good!
字寫得真好！
Superb handwriting!
實驗報告是用草書寫的
The lab report is written in cursive.
物有所值
Value for money.
他們給出的 g 值是8.2，不應該是9.8嗎？
They have given 8.2 as the value for g. Shouldn't it be 9.8?
無知的家夥！
Ignorant chap!
如果你在實驗室裏得到9.8作為 g 的值...-是的
If you get 9.8 as the value of g in the lab.. - Yes.
那你肯定是作弊了，兄弟
Then you have certainly cheated, bro.
8.2看起來更真實
8.2 seems more realistic.
即使是A1組的學生也會從他那裏買實驗報告
Even the A1 batch buys lab reports from him.
為了節省8個小時花了我700盧比
It cost me 700 rupees to save 8 hours.
300盧比，400盧比是為了租車
No. 300 rupees. 400 rupees was for the scooty rental.
你那破車我隻騎了兩天，這還要收我錢嗎？
Are you going to charge me just because I used your scooty for 2 days?
不不不，是我租的另一輛車
No, no. Not mine. The other one that I have rented.
4天隻要400盧比，是不是很劃算？
Only 400 rupees for 4 days. Isn't it great deal?
施萬吉說我做事冇有條理
Shivangi says I am not organized.
等著瞧吧
Wait and watch.
什麼另一輛？
What other one?
給誰租的? 花了我400盧比? ！
And for whom? It cost me 400 rupees?!
你想讓我們四個在一輛摩托車上疊羅漢嗎？
You expect the four of us to sit one on top of the other?
我太機智了，我已經在車裏加滿油
I am so sly. I've already filled petrol in the scooty.
- 什麼四個人?-你，我，施萬吉和瓦蒂卡
What four people? - You, me, Shivangi and Vartika.
哪個瓦蒂卡?-拉塔瓦爾
Vartika who? - Ratawal.
- 拉塔瓦爾是誰?-希萬吉的朋友
Ratawal who? - Shivangi's friend.
你在說什麼，兄弟? 講清楚一點
What are you saying, bro? Quiet. Tell me calmly.
你在說什麼？
What are you saying?
我應該保持沈默還是告訴你？
Should I remain quiet or should I tell you?
聽著，我們有4天的休息時間
Look. We have a 4 day break.
冇有輔導，冇有家庭作業
No coaching. No homework.
我們一起去遊覽科塔
We will go on an excursion.
我另外租了一輛摩托車，這樣我們四個……
I rented a scooty so that the four of us..
你，我，施萬吉和她的朋友瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦爾可以好好逛一下科塔
..you, me, Shivangi and her friend Vartika Ratawal can sight see Kota.
是不是很酷？
Isn't that cool?
我哪兒也不去，我們有4天的休息時間
I am not going anywhere. We have a 4 day break.
瓦伊巴夫和我一起複習
Vaibhav and I will revise.
你要做什麼?-學習
What will you do? - Study.
不，不，別這麼做
No, no. Don't do it.
拜亞哥說這幾天要放鬆，所以你應該放鬆
Jeetu Bhaiya said to relax, so you should relax.
哦，是的
Oh, yes.
你也會留意老師在課上說的每一句話嗎？
Do you also pay heed to everything the teachers say?
不然呢？
Is there another possibility?
你的思想如此純潔，就像我一樣
Your thoughts are so pure. Just like mine.
- 我不能去，兄弟 -去死吧！
I can't go, buddy. - Like hell!
我在車裏加了400盧比的汽油
I filled 400 rupees worth of petrol in the scooty.
還花了500盧比租車，現在你告訴我你不去了
I paid 500 rupees to rent it. Now you're telling me you won't go.
聽著，兄弟米納和我想複習一遍教學大綱
Look, bro. Meena and I want to complete the whole syllabus..
在這四天裏
..during these 4 days.
你總是這樣
You always do this, buddy.
十勝節就是被你這樣毀掉的
You ruined the Dussehra fair plans the same way.
等一下
One moment.
十勝節的時候我不在這裏
I wasn't here at the time of the Dussehra fair.
冇錯，你當時不在，現在也不在
Exactly. You weren't here then and you aren't now either.
兄弟，施萬吉最近一直躲著我
Bro. Shivangi has been avoiding me for a long time.
我不想她和我分手
I hope she doesn't break up with me.
她還冇準備好讓下一個男孩進入心房
She isn't even mean enough to wait for another boy to enter her life..
在她和我分手之前
..before she breaks up with me.
四天之內，我想去從三駕馬車到塔拉普的所有地方
Within four days I want to go everywhere from Troika to Talap..
七大奇跡之一,
..seven wonders to C V garden,
從羅陀 · 克裏希納到站立的甘尼什吉
from Radha Krishna to standing Ganeshji
那樣我們就能在科塔創造許多回憶
..so that we create so many memories here in Kota..
她就不會再想分手的事了
..even the thought of breaking up would torment her heart.
是不是很浪漫，兄弟
Basic romantic consumerism, buddy.
那就你們倆去好了
So, you go, bro.
為什麼讓我去做電燈泡？
Why are you making me the third wheel?
有些事冇有電燈泡是做不成的，兄弟
Some things can't be done without a third wheel, bro.
她不會一個人來的，大家都去她才會來
She will come if all of us go out. She won't come alone.
但是我們還要複習，兄弟
But our revision, bro.
是的，我就是這個意思
Yes, that's what I was saying. ??
-由於某些不可抗力，我們不能一起複習了-聽我說完……
Due to some unavoidable circumstances we won't be able to revise. - I am talking.
什麼? 什麼? 什麼？
What? What? What?
我們還要在4天內複習教學大綱
We have to complete the whole syllabus in 4 days.
我想放鬆，拜亞哥說的
I want to relax. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
帶我一起去吧，烏代
Take me with you, Uday.
你不會反悔吧? 答應我
You won't retract, will you? Promise me.
不會
No.
米納？
Meena?
我想我也該放鬆一下了
I think even I should go.
當然，跟我一起去吧
Of course. Come along.
- 對吧? 謝謝-明年
Right? Thank you. - Next year.
一起參加十勝節集市
For the Dussehra fair.
你去吧，我要學習
You go. I shall study.
拿著這個，給你一個遊標卡尺
Take this. A Vernier caliper for you.
謝謝
Thanks.
你在幹什麼？
What are you doing?
你不是讓我放鬆嘛，我在放鬆
Exactly what you told me to do. Relax.
實驗進行得順利嗎?-非常順利，先生
Is the coaching going well? - Very good, sir.
一定是的
It must be.
你都冇有時間寫你自己的實驗報告
You don't have time to write your own lab report.
不是的，先生-我可以容忍 g 的最大值為7
No, sir. - I can tolerate the value of g up to 7.
但我不能容忍謊言
But I cannot tolerate lies.
你們這幫培訓班的學生不尊重學校
You coaching students don't respect school.
你是第一次來學校，是嗎?-不，先生
You have come to school for the first time, haven't you? - No, sir.
- 我來過-你又在撒謊
I came. - You're lying again.
冇有，先生，我來過好幾次
No, sir. I came several times.
在食堂吃泡芙要多少錢？
How much do puffs cost in the canteen?
你以為我是白癡嗎? 我看筆跡就知道
You think I am an idiot? I can tell by looking at the handwriting..
施樂中心的小夥子寫的
..the chap at the Xerox center has written it.
這是古普塔的筆跡
This is Gupta's handwriting.
你是從神童來的，是嗎?-是的，先生
You are from Prodigy, aren't you? - Yes, sir.
你不可能來自馬赫什瓦裏
You can't be from Maheshwari.
告訴迪帕克我想見他
Tell Deepak I wish to see him.
如果他明天不來
If he doesn't come to see me by tomorrow..
我就讓所有的神童學生都不及格
..I will fail all the Prodigy students.
然後你們繼續努力學習吧
Then you can keep trying for the JEE advance.
- 明白了嗎?-是的，先生
You understand? - Yes, sir.
下一個
Next.
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦爾
Vartika Ratawal.
米納，我和烏代一起去玩
Meena. I will go with Uday.
那我怎麼辦?-你在家裏放鬆
What about me relaxing? - You relax at home.
他們要去哪裏？
Where are they going?
去遊覽科塔
To sightsee all of Kota, inside out.
這真是個好計畫
That is such a nice plan.
瓦伊巴夫，你坐烏代的車，你坐我的
Vaibhav, you hop on Uday's vehicle and you come with me.
打擾了，朋友們，你們好
Excuse me. Hello, friends.
我能和你們一起去探索科塔嗎？
Can I go with all of you to explore Kota?
你是?-米娜爾·帕雷克
You are? - Meenal Parekh.
她是書呆子……咳咳……別帶她……咳咳
(fake coughs) Nerd Alert (fake coughs) Get rid of her.
- 你好-你好
Hello. - Hi.
非常歡迎你，但我們已經有四個人了
You're most welcome, but we are already four.
我們五個人坐不下的-六個
How can five of us go? - Six.
既然大家都要去，我也要去
Now that everyone is going I shall go too.
嗨，我是瓦伊巴夫-瓦蒂卡
Hi. I'm Vaibhav. - Vartika.
小施，還是你們一起去吧? 我們改天再聚
Shiv, why don't you all leave? I'll take a rain check.
我們在路上再買個墊子-不，不，我有
So we'll buy pads on the way. - No, no. I have some.
不不，這不是月經的問題
No. No. This is not about periods.
我收到了馬赫什瓦裏的入學試卷
I received Maheshwari's sample papers..
我一道題都不會做
..and I couldn't solve any of it.
所以，我應該留下來準備一下
So, I should stay back and prepare for it.
- 我為你製定了整個假期計劃-是的
I made the entire plan for you. - Yes.
- 現在你要拋棄我們?-對不起
You're ditching us? - Sorry.
哦! 和這些無聊的人在一起
Oh! With these boring people..
- 我會覺得無聊的-她在開玩笑
..I will get bored. - She's joking.
- 我們才不無聊-是的
We are not boring. - Yes, yes.
我們都是有趣的靈魂
We are very intelligent.
這些問題有三十分鍾肯定做完了-是的
These problems will be solved in 30 minutes. - Yes.
很簡單
Very easy.
- 是的，是的，我會幫她解決的
By them. - Yes, yes. I'll help her solve it.
別擔心，夥計們
No worries, guys.
- 施萬吉，求你了-不行，瓦蒂卡，你必須去
Shivangi, please. - No. Vartika, this is not done.
- 求你了-求你了，施萬吉，求你了
Please. - Please, Shivangi. Please.
好吧，繼續學習吧
Okay. Go ahead and study.
好的，那我也不去了
Well, alright. Then I won't go either.
為什麼？
Why?
你到底要改多少次主意？
How many times will you change your mind for one plan?
我們又不是去果阿
We aren't going to Goa.
我幫助她學習，這對她有幫助
I will help her study. It will be a help to her.
無論如何，你們四個人剛好
In any case you are a group of four.
米納也能幫她學習
She will study and get help. Meena will do it.
不，我要出去玩，拜亞哥說要放鬆
No, no. I shall go out. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
冇關係，烏代，這次我會做出犧牲的
It is okay, Uday. I shall make the sacrifice this time.
冇關係-不，不，瓦巴夫，你也來
It's fine. - No, no, Vaibhav. You come too.
如果你不放鬆的話，你會精疲力盡的來吧
You will burn out if you don't relax. Come.
我給你騰個地方，來吧
We will adjust. Come.
不不，你們去吧，好好玩
No, no. You go. You guys carry on.
冇事的夥計
It's okay, buddy.
現在隻有一個空位了，對吧？
One spot is available now, right?
太棒了! 謝謝
Yeah! Thanks.
你確定你不來嗎？
You're sure you won't come?
你會錯過很多好玩的
You will miss a lot.
拿著這個米納
Hold this Meena.
我們走
Let's go.
- 再見-再見
Bye, you guys. - Bye.
別緊張，我們一起做題
Don't be tense. We will do the paper.
放鬆
Just relax.
謝謝
Thanks.
我是瓦蒂卡-拉塔瓦爾，我知道，我知道
I'm Vartika. - Ratawal. I know. I know.
對不起，你剛才自我介紹了
Sorry. You introduced yourself earlier.
好吧
Okay.
對不起，我剛才冇聽到你的名字
Sorry. Actually I didn't hear your name earlier.
這就是我再次自我介紹的原因，希望你能再說一遍名字
That's why I introduced myself again hoping you would repeat your name.
你叫什麼名字?-瓦伊巴夫，瓦伊巴夫 · 拉塔瓦爾
So, your name? - Vaibhav. Vaibhav Ratawal.
哦，對不起，我怎麼可能是拉塔瓦? 瓦伊巴夫潘迪
Oh, sorry. How can I be Ratawal? Vaibhav Pandey.
有點尷尬，不是嗎？
It was a little awkward, wasn't it?
不過別擔心
But don't worry.
我們一起解決這張試卷-好的
We will solve the paper. - Okay.
你... 對不起，放鬆點-不，不，謝謝
You.. Sorry. Just relax. - No, no. Thank you.
走吧？
Shall we?
真是諷刺! 冷咖啡是這裏最有名的菜品
What irony! The cold coffee is the most famous dish at Chai paani.
一杯冷咖啡
One cold coffee.
二杯
Two.
施凡吉，你在醫學組，是嗎？
Shivangi, you are in Medical, aren't you?
我小的時候也想成為一名醫生，但是..
I too wanted to be a doctor when I was young but..
但是什麼？
But what?
但當我長大後，我變得非常情緒化
But when I grew up I turned out to be pretty emotional.
我爸爸說醫生不能這麼情緒化
My dad said doctors can't be so emotional..
所以我選擇了工程學
..so, I chose engineering.
- 你也很情緒化?-是的
You too are emotional? - Yes.
看看這個問題-是的，問題
Look at this question. - Yes. Question.
首先，你不應該看這個問題
Firstly, you shouldn't see the question.
什麼？
what?
傑圖·拜亞說要先檢查問題的最後一行
Jeetu Bhaiya says to check the last line of the question first.
然後再檢查一下選項
Then one should check the options.
例如，這裏說，容器的溫度是多少？
For example, it says here what will the temperature of the vessel be?
看看這些選擇
Look at the options.
溫度不能用焦耳、摩爾或卡路裏來計算
The temperature can't be calculated in joules, moles or calories.
所以，選項D"25攝氏度"是正確答案
So, D 25 celcius is the correct answer.
這根本不是什麼熱量的問題
This wasn't a thermo question at all.
這是一個常識性的問題
It was a common sense question.
哦，是的! 我都冇有註意到
Oh, yes! Actually I did not pay attention.
順便問一下，你哥哥也在印度理工學院嗎？
By the way, is your brother also in IIT?
不，不，兄弟是一個複合體
No, no. Brother is a Compounder.
什麼？
What?
你是問傑圖·拜亞，拜亞哥是在印度理工-我明白了
Jeetu Bhaiya. Jeetu Bhaiya is in IIT. - I see.
他在神童教書-好的
He teaches at Prodigy. - Okay.
是的
Yes.
我也應該在一開始就參加課程
I too should have joined classes at the beginning.
現在一切都亂套了
Everything is in a mess now.
別擔心
Don't worry.
我會幫你把睏境轉變為理由
I'll convert your mess into reasons.
好的理由
Good reasons.
好吧
Okay.
我們看下一道題?-好的
Shall we do the next? - Yes.
讀最後一行
Read the last line.
別靠太近
Stay in your limits.
這裏有很好的家庭氣氛，不是嗎?-是的
This is such a good family atmosphere, isn't it? - Yes.
下次我會帶我的父母來這裏-是的
Next time I shall bring my parents here. - Yes.
烏代！
Uday!
你覺得讓他們倆單獨相處合適嗎？
You think it is proper to leave the two of them alone?
你害怕米納？
You're afraid of Meena?
我是為米納擔心
I am afraid for Meena.
你確定？
You're sure?
第一年就要結束了，但我還是不知道你的全名
The entire year is about to end but I still don't know your whole name.
米納，你姓什麼？
Meena, what is your surname?
我姓米納，我的名字叫巴爾穆昆德
My surname is Meena. My name is Balmukund Meena.
大家都可愛地叫我米納
Everybody endearingly calls me Meena.
你被親切地稱呼為什麼?-傑姆庫迪
What are you called endearingly? - Jhamkudi.
傑姆庫迪，很好聽的名字-不是嗎？
Jhamkudi. It's a nice name. - Isn't it?
是的
Yes.
米娜爾太單純了
Meenal is so straight and simple.
我打賭她不會下象棋
I bet she doesn't play the knight in chess.
難道不是嗎？
Isn't that true?
米納和米娜爾會是很好的一對，不是嗎？
Incidentally Meena and Meenal would make a nice pair, wouldn't they?
米納和米娜爾，米納和米娜爾……
Meena, Meenal. Meenal, Meena.
女士優先
Ladies first.
謝謝，瓦巴夫-謝謝？
Thanks, Vaibhav. - For?
- 你幫我解決了所有的三張試卷-是的
You helped me solve all three papers. - Yes.
一天就結束了
I got through it all in one day.
我自己可能要花七天時間才能做完
I would have taken seven days to get through it.
冇錯，我們一天就熬過來了
That's right. We got through it all in one day.
是的-剩下的幾天都冇什麼事了
Yes, that is true. - Nothing is left for the remaining days.
不，不，我還有事
No, no. I have something left.
我要複習教學大綱
I shall revise the whole syllabus.
很好
Good.
好的，如果你有什麼問題就告訴我
Okay. Let me know if you have any problem.
好的，再見
Okay. Bye-bye.
順便說一下，我可以幫助你複習！
Incidentally, I could help you with your revision. Yes!
我可以幫你複習
I could help you with your revision.
我很有天賦，我可以幫助任何人記住任何東西
I am very talented. I can help anyone memorize anything.
要我提醒你的立場嗎？
Shall I remind you of your position?
烏代，兄弟，我不能出去
Uday, bro I can't go out.
我必須要學習，很快要改組考試了
I have to study. I have my reshuffling exam. Non sense!
是的，我冇有出去，我在學習
Yes, well. I didn't go out. I was studying.
你冇在學習，無賴
You weren't studying, scoundrel.
你整天都在調情
You were clinging.
跟她
Onto her.
聽著，你今天教她解題了，是嗎？
Listen. You sat up to teach her today, didn't you?
明天教教她睡姿-閉嘴! 流氓！
Teach her in a sleeping position tomorrow. - Shut up! Scoundrel!
這是事實，不是嗎，米納？
It is the truth. Isn't that right, Meena?
他怎麼了？
What's the matter with him?
迪帕克是瘋了嗎？
Has your Deepak lost his mind?
他是不是不想開培訓班了？
Doesn't he want to run the coaching classes anymore?
我跟他說了來見你
I told him to come and see you.
- 你告訴他了?-是的
You told him? - Yes.
好吧
Well, alright.
你告訴他我的名字了嗎？
What did you tell him my name is?
我是梅塔副校長！
Vice-Principal Mehta sir.
年輕的心 -我明白了，就是你
Modern heart. - I see. That's you.
你去吧，我來對付他
You go. I will deal with him.
下一個！
Next!
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦爾
Vartika Ratawal.
“我說了”
"I said it."
“你說對了”
"You said it."
“僅此而已”
"That's all it is."
“我忍受了”
"I endured it."
“你忍受了”
"You endured it."
“但現在不是了”
"But not anymore."
再見，夥計們，再見
Bye, guys. See you.
我覺得這樣不對
I don't feel right about this.
為什麼? 你不喜歡嗎？
Why? Didn't you enjoy?
我可以教你更好的，如果你喜歡，我還會講笑話
I can teach you even better. I can even crack jokes if you like.
什麼？不，我不是這個意思
What? No, that's not what I meant.
你想和他們一起出去玩，而我卻把你留在這裏
You wanted to go out with them and I kept you here.
不不不
Oh! No. No. No.
不是這樣的
It's not that.
我也是很想學習的
Even I wanted to do my revision.
我還要準備參加馬赫什瓦裏的考試
Even I have to sit for Maheshwari's exam.
你也一樣嗎?-是的，真的
Even you have to sit for it? - Yes, really.
我為什麼要撒謊？
Why would I lie?
-我又冇說你在撒謊-冇錯
When did I say you were lying? - Yes.
是的，冇錯
Yes, exactly. Exactly.
該死！
Crap!
如果是這樣的話，那也冇關係，我們可以一起學習
If that's the case, then it's okay. We could study together.
是的，這真是個好主意
Yes, we can. It's a good idea. It's possible.
順便問一下，你選了哪個中心？
By the way, which center did you get?
我還不知道
I haven't got it as yet.
很快就知道了，等我填好錶格
I will get it. I will get it when I fill the form.
你還冇填錶嗎?-冇有
You haven't filled the form as yet? - No.
今天是最後一天
Today is the last date.
什麼？
What?
不要脫掉外套
Don't take off your jackets.
校服不要漏出來
The uniform should not be visible.
我來點單，你們坐好了
I will place the order. You sit tight.
什麼也別說
Don't say a word.
無論如何，絕對不要把身份證拿出來
No matter what, never show your I-card.
如果有人問你要身份證，驕傲地告訴他們
If anyone asks for your ID, tell them proudly.
我冇有-我冇有
I don't have it. - I don't have it.
我冇有，叔叔
I don't have it, uncle.
先生，你必須出示身份證才能坐在這裏
Sir, you have to present an ID to sit here.
為什麼?-這樣我們就能確認你的年齡了
Why do I have to present it? - So we know your age.
那你問我就好了嘛
So, ask me my age.
十七
Seventeen.
裏麵的燈光真好看?-反射
Lights were so amazing inside, weren't they? - Reflection.
我一開始就告訴你了，我們去塔拉普島吧
I told you in the first place. Let's go to Talap..
但是你根本不聽
..but you don't want to pay heed to me.
寶貝，那邊也要查身份證的
Baby, they demand IDs even over there.
那他們一定是查客人，而不是查員工
They must be demanding them from others, not from the staff.
米納，給我一支筆-好的
Meena, give me a marker. - Yes.
過來
Back.
- 謝謝-冇事
Thank you, ma'am. - Never mind that.
填好錶格，盡快交回
Fill the form and return it quickly.
你也是處女座的?-是的
You too are a Virgo? - Yes.
你也是?-不，我前男朋友是
You too? - No. My boyfriend was.
哦！
Oh!
你現在冇有男朋友?-冇有，我們分手了
You don't have a boyfriend now? - No, we broke up.
很好很好
Good. Good.
你們為什麼分手?-他從不學習
Why did you break up? - He never studies.
這樣不行，不學習怎麼行
That is wrong. That is very wrong.
我熱愛學習，學習使我快樂
I study a lot. I love studies.
我的意思是，不是所有的處女座都一樣，對吧？
I mean to say, not all Virgos are the same. Right?
有些處女座的人工作努力，有些人富有同情心
Some Virgos are hard-working. Some are compassionate.
有些是情人
Some are lovers.
友情，友情……
Friendly lovers. Friendly lovers.
刻闆印象是錯誤的
It's wrong to stereotype. It's wrong to stereotype.
你說對不對，阿姨?-填好錶格，盡快交回來
What do you think, sister? - Fill the form and return it quickly.
你對這個女孩的愛讓你悶在這裏學習，還要教她解題
Your love for the girl made you study and you even taught her.
現在你還去填寫了馬赫什瓦裏的錶格？
Now you went and filled Maheshwari's form too?
愛情是盲目的，兄弟，不是瘋狂的
Love is blind, bro, not insane.
對吧，米納？
Right, Meena?
你每天都帶他去什麼地方？
Where have you been taking him every day?
我想明年應該還會再見到你的
I guess I will see you again next year.
不，不，先生..
No, no. Sir..
我一定來參加期末考試
..I shall come for the final exam.
你會來嗎?-當然
You will come? - Certainly.
當然?-當然
Certainly? - Certainly
你保證？
Promise?
我保證
Promise.
去吧
Go there.
下一個
Next.
瓦蒂卡
Vartika.
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦爾
Vartika Ratawal.
“就像一場夢”
"Like a dream."
“就像天堂”
"Like heaven."
“這個世界曾經是”
"This world used to be."
“看，現在它在燃燒”
"Look, now it's burning."
“你問我”
"And you ask me."
“我為什麼不高興? ”
"Why I am upset?"
你家很漂亮-謝謝
Your house is very nice. - Thank you.
有時候我覺得自己像是在轉移話題
Sometimes I feel like shifting here.
- 什麼?-為了學習
Huh? - For studies.
女士優先
Ladies first.
嘿，小子!-是誰？
Hey, boy! - Who is it?
擡頭
Up. Up.
你好，叔叔-嗯，好的
Greetings, uncle. - Yes, yes. Okay, okay.
你不能進來
You cannot come in.
為什麼?-這個出租屋是女生的
Why? - This PG is for girls.
我昨天讓你進來了
I allowed you yesterday.
我還以為你是她哥哥呢-叔叔！
I thought you must be her brother. - Uncle!
我不是她哥哥-所以我才不讓你進來！
I am not her brother. - That's why I say, out!
叔叔，你把我當成她的男朋友了，是不是？
Uncle, you are confusing me for her boyfriend, aren't you?
不，我們是好朋友-走! 離開這裏！
No. Close friend. - Go! Get out of here!
這什麼人啊? 他在公開場合叫我兄弟
What kind of an uncle is he? He is publicly calling me brother.
你哥哥會生氣的-快點! 走吧！
Your brother will be offended. - Come on! Get going!
喔！
Whoo!
請等一下，先不要進來
One moment. Don't come inside. Please. Please.
你的房東阿姨在這兒，不會有問題吧？
Your aunty won't have a problem here, will she?
不，不，阿姨會有什麼問題呢？
No, no. What problem would aunty have?
烏代每天都把施萬吉帶到這裏
Uday brings Shivangi here every day.
我第一次帶女孩來-什麼？
I have brought a girl with me for the first time. - What?
我是說朋友，朋友-是的
I mean friend. Friend. - Yes.
你在瞎操心，讓我進來吧
You are needlessly worrying. Let me come in.
不! 不! 不! 不! 別進來，就兩分鍾，求你了
No! No! No! No! Don't come in. Two minutes. Please.
我見過更髒的房間
I have seen dirtier rooms.
你每天都洗澡，對吧? 這就夠了
You shower every day, right? That will suffice.
嗒噠！
Ta-dah!
請坐
Please.
那麼，我們今天要研究引力
Yes. So, we shall study gravitation today.
引力
Gravitation.
萬有引力非常的神奇
Gravitation is such a nice thing.
萬有引力有一種美麗的香味
Gravitation has a beautiful fragrance.
兩個未知的身體互相吸引
The attraction of two unknown bodies for each other.
生活在彼此的周圍
Living their lives around each other.
一圈又一圈
Round and round.
瓦伊巴夫
Vaibhav.
我們能放棄引力嗎？
Can we ditch gravitation?
為什麼?-我的力學很弱
Why? - I am very weak with SHM.
所以，可以嗎？
So, can we do that first?
好的好的，當然了，我知道力學的
Yes, yes. I know it. Why wouldn't I know SHM?
力學非常簡單
SHM is very easy.
我知道-但是我什麼時候說你不懂力學？
I know it. - But when did I say you don't know SHM?
冇有，你冇說過
Exactly. Exactly. You didn't say that. You didn't say that.
力學
SHM.
哦，糟糕! 哦，不! 到我鍛煉的時間了
Oh, crap! Oh, no! It's time for my exercise.
糟糕糟糕！
Oh, crap! Crap!
我不管你在做什麼，你怎麼能不接我的電話呢？
I don't care what you were doing. How could you not answer my call?
首先，你不用學習，你隻是到處閒逛
Firstly, you don't study. You just wander off anywhere.
寶貝，別喊，會有人聽到的
Baby, don't yell. Someone will hear you.
為什麼我不能喊？
Why shouldn't I yell?
為什麼？
因為我會改過自新，我會改變
Because I will mend my ways. I will change.
我也會學習，事實上，我正在學習
I will study too. In fact, I am studying.
力、嚮量、平衡、化合物、複合
Force. Vector. Equilibrium. Irrational. Compound. Complex.
你好
Hello.
兄弟，你知道我和施萬吉在一起，對吧？
Bro, you know I'm out with Shivangi, don't you?
那你為什麼現在給我打電話? 你破壞了一個浪漫的時刻
Then why are you calling me now? You spoiled a romantic moment.
對不起，夥計，瓦蒂卡來了-哦！
I'm sorry, buddy. Vartika has come. - Oh!
避孕套在H·C·維爾馬的書裏，第二章，半導體
Condoms are kept in H.C.Verma, part 2, the semi-conductors.
你在說什麼？
What are you saying?
我要非學院的登錄密碼
I want the login password for Unacademy.
- 你做不到的，孩子-我也不想做
'You won't be able to do it, boy.' - I don't want to do it either.
我們隻是朋友，好嗎
We are just friends, okay.
密碼就是"密碼"，小寫全拚
Its the password. All small.
他一定能考上印度理工
He's a true IITian.
為什麼？
Why?
到死都是處男
He'll die a virgin.
親愛的同學們，讓我們來看看今天的彈簧座係統
My dear students, let's have a look at the spring block system today.
這是塊，這是彈簧，如果我把彈簧拉長
This is the block. This is the spring. If I elongate the spring by..
瓦伊巴夫!-好的，馬上來，最後兩個
Vaibhav! - Yes, I'm coming. Last two.
吸氣
Breathe in.
呼氣
Breathe out.
你真的太有用了
This is very useful at the last minute.
謝謝你，兄弟
Thank you, bro.
我們全都做出來了
We did it all.
明天就要考試了，我不怕
The exam is tomorrow and I am not afraid.
我的意思是，不那麼怕了
I mean, not that much.
我隻要看一下那些末日筆記就完事了
I just have to read the doomsday notes and I'm done.
什麼筆記?-末日筆記
What notes? - Doomsday.
等等
Hold on.
這歌，最後一分鍾的複習
These. For last minute revision.
它包含了每一章的概述
It contains the overview of each chapter.
哦! 我也做了這個，等等，我給你看
Oh! I too have made this. Wait. I'll show you.
所有的考點和時間
All the topics and time.
你可以通過非學院的應用程序在任何章節觀看它
You can watch it on the Unacademy app from and to any chapter.
你一直看這個流量夠用嗎?-冇事
Don't you lose data if you check it all the time? - No.
我離線下載的-哦，我明白了
I download it offline. - Oh, I see.
你已經把這麼大的內存都裝滿了?-是的
You've filled up such a big register. Seriously? - Yes.
你為什麼對馬赫什瓦裏的入學考試這麼緊張？
Why are you so tense for Maheshwari's entrance test?
因為很難
Because it is tough.
是的，冇錯，但是我們已經都複習到位了
Yes, that it is, but we have covered everything.
怎麼了？
What's the matter?
事實上
Actually
我的哥哥是馬赫什瓦裏最好的一組
my brother was in Maheshwari's top batch.
哦!-所以，我覺得至少如果我能進入馬赫什瓦裏.
Oh! - So, I felt at least if I make it to Maheshwari..
就能獲得考上印度理工學院的信心
..I will gain confidence that I can get to IIT..
但我覺得我冇有任何機會
..but I did not feel I had any chance.
你知道我在這四天裏學到的東西比一年裏學到的還要多
You know I've learned more in these 4 days than I did through the year.
我開始覺得自己像個白癡
I had starting feeling like an idiot.
謝謝你幫我重建自信
Thanks for restoring my confidence.
你為什麼不早點來科塔？
Why didn't you come to Kota earlier?
我們本可以早點成為朋友的
We would've become friends earlier.
是的
Yes.
我能說什麼呢？
What can I say?
你不告訴我們也冇關係，但一定要告訴她
It's okay if you don't tell us, but make sure you tell her.
一旦明天考試結束，天知道你什麼時候能再見到她
Once the exam gets over tomorrow, Lord knows when you'll see her again.
環境已經創造好了，兄弟，嚮她錶白吧
The mood is set, bro. Propose to her.
聽著，明天是個好日子，對吧? 拿著這個
Listen. Tomorrow is an auspicious day, right? Take this.
穿得精神點
Go in style.
“就像一場夢”
"Like a dream."
“就像天堂”
"Like heaven."
“這個世界曾經是”
"This world used to be."
“看，現在它在燃燒”
"Look, now its burning."
“你問我”
"And you ask me."
“我為什麼不高興? ”
"Why I am upset?"
“事情不會再按你的方式發展了”
"Things won't work your way anymore."
“說吧”
"Say it."
“此時此刻”
"Now and here."
“愛情萬歲”
"Long live love."
哥，有酸奶嗎?-有
Bhaiya, you have yogurt? - Yes, you can have yogurt.
在那
Take it from there.
還有..
And...
糖?-有的
Sugar? - We have sugar too. There you go, bhaiya.
多少錢?-三十盧比
How much? - Thirty rupees, bhaiya. 30.
謝謝你
Thank you.
這是什麼？
What is this?
今天是個好日子
Today is an auspicious day.
這能帶來好運-哦，好吧
So, this is auspicious. - Oh, okay.
如果你吃酸奶，緊張情緒就會消失
If you eat yogurt your nervousness will disappear.
你也吃，你也要考試
You eat it too. You too are sitting for the exam.
是的，哦! 我也要考試
Yes, oh! I too am sitting for the exam.
我們現在該怎麼辦?-我不知道
What do we do with this now? - I don't know.
我們把它塗在頭髮上吧
Let's apply it on our hair.
它會使頭發有光澤-惡心！
It will make the hair lustrous. - Gross!
我開玩笑的
I'm joking.
我不是告訴過你我冇那麼無聊嗎?-是的
Didn't I tell you, I'm not that boring? - Yeah.
我們吃完吧-好
Let's finish it. - Yeah.
“愛情萬歲! ”
"Long live love!"
“上麵寫著... ..
"It is written..
用紅墨水寫的
..in red ink."
“我的動機是叛逆的”
"My motives are rebellious."
“看，現在它在燃燒”
"Look, now it's burning."
“你問我”
"And you ask me."
“我為什麼不高興? ”
"Why I am upset?"
“事情不會再按你的方式發展了”
"Things won't work your way anymore."
“說吧”
"Say it."
“現在和這裏”
"Now and here."
“愛情萬歲”
"Long live love."
“愛情萬歲! ”
"Long live love!"
“我的夢想... ..
"My dreams..
和夢想聯合起來，你要知道”
..have united with dreams. Know that."
“我的動機... ..
"My motives..
動機是一緻的，要知道”
..have united with motives. Know that."
“愛情萬歲! ”
"Long live love!"
不是印度理工學院，我要參加 sat 考試，我想去美國
Not IIT. I will sit for the SATs. I want to go to US.
康奈爾，耶魯，哈佛，哥倫比亞
Cornell, Yale, Harvard, Columbia. One of these.
什麼？
What?
我叔叔在那邊，他叫我去的
My uncle is over there. He told me to come.
那你為什麼在這裏學得這麼辛苦？
Then why are you working so hard over here?
為了知識，多學有冇有壞處
For knowledge. Knowledge doesn't get wasted.
烏代，帶我一起走
Uday, take me with you.
這個世界上冇有人會永遠呆在一個地方
Nobody in this world stays put in one place.
怎麼了？
What's the matter?
- 我已經在等結果了-是的
I'm already eager for the results. - Yes.
不過需要兩個星期-是的
It will take two weeks though. - Yes.
好的，再見
Okay, then. Bye.
再見
Bye.
See you.
瓦蒂卡-嗯
Vartika. - Yes.
怎麼了
Yes.
瓦蒂卡，你... 你會早點睡覺，是嗎？
Vartika you... you will go to bed early, won't you?
- 平靜地-是的
Peacefully. - Yes.
你也是
You too.
是的，我也是
Yes. Me too.
好吧，晚安-晚安
Okay, then. Goodnight. - Goodnight.
保持聯係-好的
Stay in touch. - Yes.
該死！
Crap!
瓦伊巴夫!-瓦蒂卡
Vaibhav! - Vartika.
我們可以開始12年級的教學大綱了嗎？
Can we begin the syllabus for the 12th?
是的，當然可以
Yes, we could do that.
- 明天-明天
Tomorrow. - Tomorrow.
酷
Cool.
- 晚安-晚安
Goodnight. - Goodnight.
再見
Bye.
“我說，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意”
"If she agrees."
“如果她用眼睛唱搖籃麯”
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
“我會飄進夢裏”
"I will float into dreams."
“阻止我”
"Stop me."
“我說，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意見麵... ..
"If she agrees to meet ..
然後花點時間
and spends a few moments."
“我會錶達我的感受”
"I'll express my feelings."
“請阻止我”
"Please stop me."
“哦，請阻止我”
"Oh please stop me."
“但請不要阻止我們... ..
"But please don't stop us..
. . 當我們迷失在這種方式.
..when we are lost in this manner..
在我們的小世界裏
..in our small world."
“你為什麼要阻止我們? ”
"Why would you stop us?"
有時在我們忙碌的生活中，找到了愛情，但愛情卻離開了我們
Sometimes in our busy lives we find love, love leaves us.
或者永遠堅持下去
or holds on forever.
這首浪漫的歌觸動了你的心靈
This romantic track to touch your hearts.
在科塔七大奇跡不夠用
The seven wonders that are made in Kota are less.
你是第八大奇跡，我的愛人
You are the eighth wonder, my love.
再見
Bye.
愛你，想你，麼麼麼
Love you. Miss you. Take care.
這將持續六個月
This will last another six months.
夥計，我應該好好學習的
Buddy, I should have studied.
很多時間被浪費了，因為我想放鬆
A lot of time was wasted because I wanted to relax.
甚至學習也可以很放鬆，兄弟
Even studies can be very relaxing, bro.
你隻是需要一個合適的搭檔
You just need the right partner.
“你能想象... ..
"Can you imagine..
當我們迷失的時候
..when we are lost..
在星空中
..in the stars."
“你怎麼找到我們? ”
"How would you find us?"
“我說，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意”
"If she agrees."
“如果她用眼睛唱搖籃麯”
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
“我會飄進夢裏”
"I will float into dreams."
“阻止我”
"Stop me."